https://www.unitedwire.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Home > Privacy Policy
United Wire General Web Site Privacy Statement
United Wire has a long-standing commitment to safeguard the privacy of information entrusted to us. The privacy principles and procedures set forth below are intended to tell you how we collect, use, and distribute user information via our primary public web site (www.unitedwire.com). This statement also applies generally to all web sites operated by United Wire (and its affiliates). This statement does not cover information collected from sources other than United Wire web sites.
United Wire General Web Site Privacy Statement covers the following topics:
Specific United Wire sites and services
Types and uses of personal information
Sharing with other United Wire companies
How personal information is shared with third parties
Security measures
Modifications to statement
Access and accuracy
Data retention
Children
Linked Web sites
Use of cookies
Specific United Wire sites and services
United Wire offers a wide variety of products and services, and operates through a number of web sites. Many of these have their own privacy statements that describe the specific data collection and use practices of the particular product, service, or site. We encourage you to review the privacy statements for those sites, services, and products that you use. Unless more-specifically addressed (or to the extent otherwise provided) in those other privacy statements, the terms of this General Privacy Statement govern your interaction with United Wire.
Types and uses of personal information
If you use this web site, personally identifiable information about you may be collected and processed by United Wire employees. In general, we only collect such information (such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and type of business) when you knowingly provide it to us. Additionally, United Wire may automatically collect or process personally identifiable data (such as your Internet domain or IP address) as part of the operation of this web site or during the course of your activities on or use of this web site. In nearly all cases this data may be collected or processed by, and transferred to, United Wire facilities in the United States and in other countries where United Wire does business; the data is then subject to the legal systems of those countries. By using this web site (which resides in part on servers located in the United States), you unambiguously consent to any collection, processing, transfer or use of any personal data. If you do not consent to any collection, processing, transfer or use of such information, please discontinue use of this web site.
Sharing with other United Wire companies
We share much of our data, including personally identifiable information about you, with our affiliates throughout the world. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will follow privacy practices no less protective than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law.
How personal information is shared with third parties
Without the user’s consent, United Wire will not sell, trade, or disclose the user’s personally identifiable information to third parties that want to market products to the user. However, United Wire may disclose information to third parties assisting us in carrying out a transaction or providing a service for you (e.g., packaging, sending and delivering purchases and information to you, clearing credit card transactions, or performing statistical analyses of our services), or in connection with merger and acquisition discussions. Additionally, United Wire may disclose information when required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process, or in response to activities that are unlawful or a violation of United Wire rules for use of the web site, or to protect and defend the rights or property of United Wire.
Security measures
United Wire has implemented technological and operational security processes to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration, or unintentional destruction. While no security measure can guarantee against compromise, United Wire regularly reviews and updates its security measures in an effort to provide appropriate security for all information held by United Wire.
Modifications to statement
United Wire reserves the right to change, modify, or update this statement at any time without notice. We indicate the date of the current statement below, so you know when it was last updated.
Access and accuracy
United Wire wants to maintain only accurate information about users of the site. You can request individual information that has been gathered about you by contacting United Wire. Upon receipt of appropriate identification information, United Wire will provide you with access to the personally identifiable information that it maintains about your use of United Wire web sites or which you have supplied to United Wire via a United Wire web site. If you find factual inaccuracies, please notify United Wire so that they may be corrected.
Data retention
United Wire will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purpose it was collected.
Children
United Wire takes children’s privacy seriously. United Wire asks children under the age of 13 not to send any personally identifiable information to United Wire web sites without the consent of their parents or guardians. United Wire encourages all parents and guardians to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of personal information on the Internet. United Wire will not knowingly collect, use, or disclose to third parties any personal information collected from children, and we are committed to complying with applicable laws and requirements, such as the United States’ Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).
Linked Websites
We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy statement posted on these (and all) third party sites. United Wire is not responsible for the privacy statements or practices of sites and services controlled by other companies or organizations.
Use of cookies
United Wire may use “cookies” in connection with operation of its web sites. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on your computer by the United Wire web site server. Cookies are used for record-keeping purposes—the stored information can be retrieved by the United Wire web site server when you return to the web site. This allows United Wire to personalize or regulate the use of the site, and also permits United Wire to automate the access and data-entry functions of the site (e.g., login information), to store on-line ordering information for purchases you may make while visiting the site, and to tailor the appearance or presentation of the site to your preferences or interests. In general, we do not use cookies to track the navigational habits of identified users without the user’s consent. If you visit our sites to read or download content, much of the information we do collect is statistical only (e.g., the domain from which you access the Internet, the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site) and not personally identifiable. We use this information about the number of visitors and their use of the sites in aggregate form to make our sites more useful and attractive to you.
The use of cookies is common in the industry, and they are used at most major web sites. Cookies will not be used to pass any information from your computer except the specific information placed into the cookie from one participating United Wire web site when the cookie is retrieved by another participating United Wire web site. You may wish to adjust your Web browser to inform you whenever a cookie is to be used, or to reject all cookies automatically. However, if you elect not to accept cookies, some parts of the web site may not function properly or permit access. For more information on cookies, see https://www.cookiecentral.com/faq.htm.
Contact information
Customers should direct comments or questions regarding this statement to their United Wire representative; employees to their Personnel representative; all other inquiries should be directed to info@unitedwire.com.
Last updated: 12 June 2006 Version 1.5
UNITED WIRE
Serving Industry Since 1825
Contact Us For A Quote
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkPrivacy policy
